

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Email hello_saurabhdubey@outlook.com

Mobile (+91) 9971370912

Total work experience
5 Years 3 Months

Social Link www.linkedin.com/in/saurabh-dubey-71a1421b2

KEY SKILLS

Java

Selenium Webdriver

Rest Assured

UI Automation

API Testing

Jenkins

GIT

Cucumber

Testng

Maven

Mobaxterm

Postman

JMeter

Alm Application Lifecycle Management

Agile Methodology

Saurabh Dubey

Software Test Automation Engineer

PROFILE SUMMARY

Experience of more than 5+ years in IT industry with top key skills as Core Java, Selenium webdriver, Selenium RC, Selenium IDE, Selenium Grid, TestNG, OOPS. Highly committed to meet the deadlines, quick learner. Keen to learn new technologies.

EDUCATION

2015

B.Tech/B.E.

Arya Institute of Engineering & Technology, Jaipur

WORK EXPERIENCE

Aug 2021 -Present **Software Test Automation Engineer**

EPAM Systems

Project: MASTERCARD I have been working with Epam since three years and four months. i'm a part of well known Card & Payment domain client. My designation is acting testing lead where i handle all the testing related activities.

Aug 2020 - Aug 2021 **Quality Analyst**

Synapses LLC

Project: Wear Your Opinion Worked as a Quality Analyst

Mar 2019 - Jun 2020 **Quality Service Specialist**

Urbanclap Technologies India Pvt. Ltd.

Project: UrbanClap Worked as a Quality Service Specialist where my role was to automate test scripts according to the product based scenarios.

OTHER PERSONAL DETAILS

City New Delhi

Country INDIA

LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi